

Fahmi Nurcahya Software Engineer

- Karawana, Indonesia.
- fahminurcahya@gmail.com
- +6285718456591

PROFILE

3+ years of experience as a Software Engineer, I excel in designing, developing, and managing efficient and reliable software solutions. I possess a profound understanding of modern programming languages, software architecture, and best practices in application development.

I have actively contributed to high-quality, complex software development projects that meet client needs.

Furthermore, I am committed to continuous learning and growth within the realm of technology.

SOCIAL

- (7) fahminurcahya
- ₩ fahminurcahya
- @ afahminurcahya

EDUCATION

Bechelor of Informatic Engineering

EXPERIENCE

MIDDLEWARE DEVELOPER

July 2021 - July 2023 | PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia

- Created RestAPI service in ESB to integrate the requirements between BRI channels and thirdparty entities.
- Integrated applications with various formats such as JSON, ISO, and WSDL.
- Developed stored procedures in SQL Server.
- Acted as a dedicated middleware programmer for the BRI insurance platform (BRISURF).
- Designed the system's application flow, created API specification documentation, and conducted
- Developed dashboard applications using React.js and Express.js.
- Conducted problem-solving and monitored services using Kibana.
- Implemented technologies such as Redis, Kafka, Elasticsearch, Bitbucket, and Bamboo.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

July 2020 - Juni 2021 | PT Xsis Mitra Utama, placement at PT AZEC Indonesia Management Service

- Developed several dashboard applications using Golang, AngularJS, and Docker as containers for the applications.
- Enhanced new features on existing dashboards using Java.
- Created API services using Golang as the programming language on the server side, with PostgreSQL as the database.

BOOTCAMP JAVA DEVELOPER

December 2019 - Juni 2020 | PT Xsis Mitra Utama

- Bootcamp as a java developer

SKILLS

Web Apps

HTML5 / CSS / Boostrap Javascript / Typescript / ReactJs / AngularJS (ES5/ES6)

Node Js / Express Js (ES5/ES6)

PHP (Laravel)

Golang

Java (Spring Boot)

RDBMS(MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL)

University Of Singaperbangsa Karawang 2015-2019 MongoDB Redis

Mobile Apps

Dart / Flutter framework Kotlin Java

Others

Git, Docker, Microservices, Product Software AG, Figma / Canva / Adobe Ilustrator, Firebase, Push Notofication, Adsanse Mobile

PORTOFOLIO & CERTIFICATES

Show Portofolio